Now the next step,
下一步
is to style this section right here where we have the day.
是对这部分设置样式
So what we are going to do is we're actually going to make our own component for this,
我们将为这一部分创建一个组件
we will call it metric card.
称之为 MetricCard
And then, what we're going to do is, we'll need react.
然后 我们需要导入 react
The react native components we will need,
还需要导入
new style sheet as well as text,
View、StyleSheet 和 Text
which are all coming from react native.
它们都来自 react-native 组件
And then, we will need our date header component.
接着 导入 DateHeader 组件
We're going to go ahead and grab,
从 helpers 文件中
get metric meta info from our helper's file.
导入 getMetricMetaInfo
Then at last, what we need is our grey color which is coming from you utils/colors.
最后 从 utils/colors 中导入 grey
This is going to be a state less functional component.
这将是一个无状态函数式组件
It's going to take in a date as well as all of
它将接收 date 以及所有的指标
the metrics and we are going to return a view.
返回一个 view
So now we're going to do is,
现在
if there is a date,
如果存在 date
then we are going to render our date header,
则渲染 DateHeader
passing it the specific date.
传入特定的 date
But if there is not a date,
如果没有 date
then we do not want to render anything.
则不需要渲染任何内容
Next, what we're going to do is,
接着
we're going to say object.keys
输入 object.keys(metrics)
metrics which will give us an array with all of the items being the keys in metrics,
获得一个数组 所有项目是指标的键
and then we're going to call dot map on that.
然后对其调用 .map
We've seen this before and then from here,
我们之前见过这些代码
this will be the metric.
在这里输入 metric
And now what we're going to do is,
现在
we will say get icon,
输入 getIcon
display name, get all these properties off of that unit as well as background color.
displayName… 获取所有的属性 包括 unit 和 backgroundColor
It's going to be coming from whatever we get return from
来自于 getMetricMetaInfo 返回的信息
get metric meta info passing it the specific metric.
向 getMetricMetaInfo 传入特定的 metric
And then the UI for this section,
然后是这部分的 UI
is going to be a view.
将为一个视图
Let's go ahead and give this a style of styles.metric and a key,
设定 style= 以及 key
because we are mapping the key is going to be the metric itself.
我们将映射键 键将为 metric 本身
So let's go ahead and make that style real quick.
快速设置该 styles
So this is going to be pretty small,
内容很少
all is going to say as we will set flex direction to
只需将 flexDirection 设为 row
row and then we will give margin top of 12.
然后将 marginTop 设为 12
So now what we're going to do is,
现在
we want to call get icon.
我们将调用 getIcon
So that's going to show the icon for that specific metric.
以便显示该特定指标的图标
And then we will have another view section down here and what we want to show and again,
然后在下面设置另一个视图
all we're doing is we're recreating this section right here.
现在我们的任务是创建这部分
So what we want to show is the display name.
因此我们想显示 displayName
Let's give this a font size of 20.
将 fontSize 设为 20
And then below this what we want to do,
在下面 我们将...
so here we have the display name.
这里是显示名称
Below it, we want to show the specific value and the unit.
在下面我们想显示具体的值和单位
So what we can do is,
因此
we will say metrics at metric,
输入 metrics[metric]
then we will say unit and then now what we want to do is,
然后输入
let's say font Size 16 color is going to be grey.
现在将 say fontSize 设为 16 color 设为 gray
I think that looks pretty good.
我认为一切挺正常
Now what we need to do is,
现在我们要做的是
import metric card inside of our history file.
在 History 文件中导入 metricCard
Then now instead of just rendering this right here,
现在 我们不再渲染这部分内容
what we can do is,
而是
we will say a metric card.
输入 metricCard
Metrics is going to be metrics which we're getting right
metrics= metrics 来自于这里
here and then let's go ahead and pass it the date,
然后传入 date
which is going to be the formatted date.
将为 formattedDate
So now what we should see,
现在 看看应用效果
if everything is working correctly, is that's normal.
如果一切正常的话 这是正常的
But when we go to a day that is filled out,
选择填写了信息的日期
we get this UI right here.
我们获得了这个 UI
So it looks great on IOS.
在 IOS 上看起来不错
Let's check it on Android.
看看在 Android 上的效果
And it also looks great on Android.
在 Android 上看起来也不错